http://www.percipion.com/privacy.htm

Percipion Home
Site Map
Homeschool topicsIn the news...Internet resourcesLegal informationReady-to-use resourcesShopWho we arePercipion Home
Homeschool Fact:
Almost one-quarter of home school students are enrolled one or more grades above their age-level peers in public and private schools.
Contact Info
If you need to contact us, please us the
WebSupport Contact Form
Privacy Policy Thank you for visiting Percipion.com. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit Percipion, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. When you visit Percipion.com, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information. In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved. This information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and your personal information is not identified. If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will only be used for the purposes you authorized. This information will not be disclosed to third parties or other agencies, unless required by U.S. state or federal law. If you have other questions about the Percipion privacy policies, or have suggestions on how these policies can be improved, please feel free to e-mail us using our online support form.
© 2004-2011 Percipion, Inc - Privacy PolicySite design by e-prov.net
